# PRANAV SHARMA

REACT.JS DEVELOPER

## Experience

### React.js Developer at <u>Aartas Care Private Limited</u>

[12/10/2022-Present]

Working as a React.js Developer and developing company's Dashboard from scratch.

**Skills:** React Js, JavaScript, Html5 Css3 bootstrap Rest API, JSON, Azure DevOps(non-certified), Azure App Service(non-certified), Express JS.

## Front End Developer at Addon Shareware Private Limited

[12/04/2022-10/10/2022]

Delivered several projects to the clients of the company and made clients satisfied with my work.

**Skills:** JQuery, JavaScript, Html5 Css3 bootstrap Rest API, Figma, Adobe Illustrator.

#### Internship in My Mobi Force

[15/10/2021-10/12/2021]

Completed Internship as Technical Support.

## Education

#### Indira Gandhi National Open University

[01/2021- Present]

Pursuing bachelor's degree in computer application.

#### **CSI Polytechnic College**

[06/06/2016 - 10/05/2019]

Completed Diploma in Electronics and Communication Engineering with first division with distinction.

## Skillset

**Skills I have:** - HTML5, CSS3, BOOTSTRAP, JAVASCRIPT, JQUERY, REACTJS, RESTAPI, ExpressJS, Azure DevOps(non-certified), Azure AppService(non-certified).

Skills I am Learning: React Native, MYSQL.

## **Local Projects**

Spareo Motors - A Car service Website (Currently in Progress)

GitHub Link - https://cyberpunkpranav.github.io/SPAREO-MOTORS/Public/

**Rock Paper Scissors** 

GitHub link - https://cyberpunkpranav.github.io/Rock\_Paper\_Scissor/

Blackjack - A Card Game

GitHub Link- https://cyberpunkpranav.github.io/BlackJack/

Counter - A counting web app

GitHub - https://cyberpunkpranav.github.io/Counter/

Drum Kit - A music instrument web app
GitHub link - https://cyberpunkpranav.github.io/Drumkit/

PROFILE

I am a hardworking and ambitious individual with a great passion for software. I have great communication skills which enable me to effectively communicate with a wide range of people. I am seeing a Full-time position in the industry in which I can put into practice my knowledge and experience, ultimately benefiting the operations of the organization that I work for.

CONTACT - 7339023531

LINKED IN - <u>www.linkedin.com/in/pranav-sharma-618914187</u>

**GIT HUB** 

https://github.com/Cyberpunkpranav

EMAIL -<u>pranavsharma733902@gmail.com</u>

ADDRESS - C-64 East Jawahar Nagar Loni

Road Ghaziabad Uttar Pradesh-201102.

# HOBBIES

I like to listen to music playing games and reading Books.

FATHER'S NAME

Himanshu

DATE OF BIRTH

18 December 2000

MARTIAL STATUS

Unmarried

NATIONALITY

Indian

LANGUAGES

Hindi - Fluent, Mother tongue.

English - Intermediate, Secondary language.